Preliminary Inventory to the Forrest Caraway Papers, 1926-1960
Hoover Institution Archives
Forrest Caraway Papers,
1926-1960
64009
Caraway, Forrest, 1909-
2 manuscript boxes, 1 envelope (0.8 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, orders, and photographs, relating to the Korean War, and to the Bonus March on Washington in 1932.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Access Points
United States. Army--Officers; Bonus Expeditionary Force, 1932; Korean War, 1950-1953; Korea; United States--Politics and government; United States--Armed Forces
Container List
- Personnel 201 file (Box 1.)
- Orders, training memoranda
  - 1926-1934
  - 1934-1939
  - 1939-1942
  - 1942-1951
- Family correspondence
  - 1952
  - 1953 January (while stationed in Korea)
  - 1953 February-March (Box 2.)
  - 1953 April-August
  - 1953 September-December
  - 1954
- General orders, memoranda, photograph of the Bonus March, 1932
- Miscellaneous
- Photographs: 7 prints depicting Caraway during his military career, 1941-1956; 4 prints depicting Heartbreak Ridge, Korea, during the Korean War, 1953. Prints are labeled (Box A)